<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CodeCrusaders</title>
    <link>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CodeCrusaders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 16:22:09 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://blogger.technokoning.nl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Nsxt Powercli Export Loadbalancer</title>
      <link>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/code/nsxt-powercli-export-loadbalancer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 17:28:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/code/nsxt-powercli-export-loadbalancer/</guid>
      <description>ow to export NSX-T loadbalancer information with PowerCLI? This question popped in my mind after a customer request to generate a list with their loadbalancers and associated virtual servers. This was not as easy as I thought! First of all, the NSX-T userinterface is not very export-friendly and i could not find a way to export data. That doesn’t matter though, because I am an automation kinda guy anyways. So I thought let’s take a look at PowerCLI for NSX-T.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Lab for Kubernetes</title>
      <link>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/article/2023/online-lab-for-kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 17:22:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/article/2023/online-lab-for-kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>Good news everyone! I passed my CKA Exam and I got a pass on the first try. To practice I used an online lab and I have to say, I am a fan. This is why I am going to share how I set up an online lab for Kubernetes. How it was set up, how I used it and why it is so great. Little disclaimer, it is not a free solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Demo</title>
      <link>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/article/some-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 11:44:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/article/some-demo/</guid>
      <description> puts &amp;#34;Hello World&amp;#34; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testcode</title>
      <link>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/article/testcode/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 15:57:45 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/article/testcode/</guid>
      <description>CLICK ME We can hide anything, even code! puts &amp;#34;Hello World 1&amp;#34; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/status/bilberry-theme-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 10:45:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/status/bilberry-theme-released/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m glad to announce the release of the Bilberry Hugo theme. This premium theme is published under an open-source license (MIT), and you can use it free of charge. It took me a significant amount of time to create and refine this theme. This theme is a collaborative effort of numerous volunteers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support and Discussions</title>
      <link>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/article/support-and-discussions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 18:10:14 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/article/support-and-discussions/</guid>
      <description>Support for this theme is provided through the Issues and Discussions sections of the project. Please use the Issues section if you would like to report a defect or bug. For any other requests, use the Discussions section.
Please use the following guidelines if you want to start a discussion:
For any questions regarding a specific feature, or if you need help using or customizing the theme, use the Questions &amp;amp; Answers (Q&amp;amp;A) category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Trip to Scotland</title>
      <link>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/gallery/my-trip-to-scotland/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 18:01:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/gallery/my-trip-to-scotland/</guid>
      <description>In June 2017 I&amp;rsquo;ve visited Scotland with my best friend for two weeks. We drove a lot through the beautiful countryside and saw a lot of different animals: cattle, deer, birds, dolphins, and sheep. Sheep everywhere!
At one beautiful camping site, we saw cattle in fog in the very early morning and took a picture of it. The image now has the title &amp;ldquo;Rindviecher im Nebel&amp;rdquo;, a quite funny German phrase that means cattle in the fog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kilez More - Life And Death Of The Hegemony</title>
      <link>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/video/kilez-more-leben-und-tod-des-imperialismus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 16:23:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/video/kilez-more-leben-und-tod-des-imperialismus/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kilez More is a great Austrian musician.
Most of his songs have a political background and have amazing lyrics!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kilez More - New World Order</title>
      <link>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/audio/kilez-more-new-world-order/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 16:12:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/audio/kilez-more-new-world-order/</guid>
      <description>With the audio post type you can easily integrate a Spotify, SoundCloud, TuneIn or Mixcloud player to your post.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t want to embed sound but use a header image you can set it with the featuredImage option in your markdown file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duckduckgo.com</title>
      <link>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/link/duckduckgo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 13:05:27 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/link/duckduckgo/</guid>
      <description>A search engine that respects your privacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edward Snowden About Privacy</title>
      <link>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/quote/edward-snowden-privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 13:01:14 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/quote/edward-snowden-privacy/</guid>
      <description>Arguing that you don&amp;rsquo;t care about the right to privacy because you have nothing to hide is no different than saying you don&amp;rsquo;t care about free speech because you have nothing to say.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating Uniform Portgroups on VSphere Distributed Switch With Ansible</title>
      <link>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/article/2020/creating-uniform-portgroups-vsphere-distributed-switch-ansible/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 15:36:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blogger.technokoning.nl/article/2020/creating-uniform-portgroups-vsphere-distributed-switch-ansible/</guid>
      <description>If you are a vSphere administrator managing environments with multiple clusters and vSphere Distributed Switches, then you are probably aware that naming portgroups can sometimes be quite a challenge.
Especially when similar portgroups have to exist on more than one vSphere Distributed Switch (VDS), because you can’t have duplicate portgroup names within one vCenter. To avoid clutter you want to create those portgroups in an uniform and automated way. Well, at least i do.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
