<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CodeCrusaders</title>
    <link>https://blog.codecrusaders.nl/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CodeCrusaders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 14:58:29 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://blog.codecrusaders.nl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover Govc: set and sync vCenter permissions</title>
      <link>https://blog.codecrusaders.nl/code/2023/discover-govc-vcenter-permissions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 14:58:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.codecrusaders.nl/code/2023/discover-govc-vcenter-permissions/</guid>
      <description>No longer than a couple of weeks ago I stumbled on this nifty little tool called govc. Sure, I heard of this before, but I did not realize how powerful this tool can be. Until now! So, I decided to write a blog about my specific use-case, Set and sync vCenter permissions with an openLDAP group.
What is govc Govc is basicly a wrapper around GO modules for vSphere. To be more specific, it relies on the official VMware govmomi library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Kubecon 2023 Like a Newbie</title>
      <link>https://blog.codecrusaders.nl/gallery/2023/navigating-kubecon-2023-like-a-newbie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 17:27:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.codecrusaders.nl/gallery/2023/navigating-kubecon-2023-like-a-newbie/</guid>
      <description>Intro This year the KubeCon + CloudNativeCon 2023 event took place in the RAI Amsterdam. With 10k+ tickets sold the event was completely sold out. For me and for over 5000 (!) other attendees this was the first in person visit to KubeCon + CloudNativeCon ever. To me this underlines the importance of cloudnative and it&amp;rsquo;s eco-system. Also, enough material and impressions to write an article on how to &amp;lsquo;Navigating Kubecon 2023 Like a Newbie&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Lab for Kubernetes</title>
      <link>https://blog.codecrusaders.nl/article/2023/online-lab-for-kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 17:22:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.codecrusaders.nl/article/2023/online-lab-for-kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>Good news everyone! I passed my CKA Exam and I got a pass on the first try. To practice I used an online lab and I have to say, I am a fan. This is why I am going to share how I set up an online lab for Kubernetes. How it was set up, how I used it and why it is so great. Little disclaimer, it is not a free solution.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
